MATT GEHRLS

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-taught full stack developer, who has honed technical proficiency in web development through various projects and hands-on experience. Previous experience in the real estate industry, working to develop and market properties. A Bachelors in Music Education shows an ability to collaborate and communicate in a creative environment.

WORK HISTORY

Real Estate Transaction Coordinator, 01/2019 to 05/2022 Five Star Real Estate - Grand Rapids, MI

- Led successful completion of 300+ home sales transactions, generating \$1M in revenue over 3 years.
- Collaborated with diverse stakeholders, including buyers, sellers, attorneys, and contractors, to facilitate smooth transactions and achieve mutual objectives.
- Contact: Danielle Robinson 616-813-2095

Maintenance Supervisor, 01/2018 to 12/2018

Here 2 Serve Property Management - Grand Rapids, MI

- Greeted clients, showed apartments, and prepared leases.
- Delivered emergency 24-hour on-call service for tenants on building issues.
- Managed crew of 6 to efficiently maintain and improve 300 housing and commercial units.
- Implemented skill-based task assignment system that improved maintenance efficiency
- Contact: -Doug Pettibone Managing Broker (616) 516-5471

Realtor, 01/2015 to 01/2018

Keller Williams Realty - Grand Rapids, M

- Advertised client properties through websites, social media, and real estate guides.
- Developed and presented proposals to clients to raise awareness of potential real estate investments.
- Compared recently sold area properties to determine competitive market prices.

CONTACT

Address: Grand Rapids, MI 60602

Phone: 616-500-2366

Email: mattgehrls@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BM, Music Education, 12/2013 Western Michigan University -

Kalamazoo, MI

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Next.JS
- Sveltekit
- MongoDB
- Typescript
- Written Communication
- · Dependable and Responsible
- · Analytical and Critical Thinking

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Active volunteer and participant in local Grand Rapids development community
- · Open to Hybrid/Remote.
- Completed Frontend Developer Career Path through Scrimba
- Employee of the Year 2012 Western Michigan University Student Recreation Center